<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eden Health</title>
    <link>http://getedenhealth.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eden Health</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 19:50:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://getedenhealth.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Eden Health Mobile app</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;script&gt;
  window.location = &#39;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/eden-health/id1201859973?ls=1&amp;mt=8&#39;;
&lt;/script&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consent to Treatment 0.0.01</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/policies/consent-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/policies/consent-app/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Via this app, Eden Health provides an encrypted service through which to primarily communicate with your care team. When you register, you will also receive email/mobile notifications letting you know that you have a communication from your care team on the Eden Health app, as well as certain other electronic communications from Eden Health, that are not encrypted and may contain certain protected health information (PHI), to identify the type of communication you have received from your care team, to respond to requests you may have initiated by email or outside of the Eden Health App, and other circumstances as outlined in our &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/hipaa&#34;&gt;HIPAA Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/terms&#34;&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;terms-of-service&#34;&gt;TERMS OF SERVICE&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Eden Health! Eden Health Medical, PC (&amp;ldquo;Eden Health&amp;rdquo;) and its affiliated Eden Health, Inc. entity (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Companies,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;) offer a service that allows Users (defined below) to manage their health using online-enabled technology, enhanced digital health tools and other services (the &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) through its online platform located at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.getedenhealth.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.getedenhealth.com/&lt;/a&gt; (the &amp;ldquo;Website&amp;rdquo;) and mobile device application (&amp;ldquo;App&amp;rdquo;). Please read these Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;), the &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/privacy&#34;&gt;Eden Health Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; (the &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo;), the &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/hipaa&#34;&gt;Eden Health HIPAA Policy&lt;/a&gt; (the &amp;ldquo;HIPAA Policy&amp;rdquo;), the &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/terms&#34;&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; and any notices on the Website carefully because they govern your use of the Service. For purposes of these Terms, the term &amp;ldquo;User&amp;rdquo; includes members, whose membership has been secured via contract with the member’s employer or otherwise, and non-member users of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THESE TERMS OF SERVICE REQUIRE BINDING ARBITRATION ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS TO RESOLVE DISPUTES, RATHER THAN JURY TRIALS, AND INCLUDE A CLASS ACTION WAIVER. THESE TERMS LIMIT THE REMEDIES THAT MAY BE AVAILABLE TO YOU IN THE EVENT OF A DISPUTE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By using the Service, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you object to anything in these Terms, do not use the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acceptance-of-terms-of-service&#34;&gt;Acceptance of Terms of Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Electronic Agreement.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; These Terms are an electronic contract that set out the legally binding terms of your use of and subscription to the Service. By using the Service (including by clicking the &amp;ldquo;I accept&amp;rdquo; button associated with these Terms), you accept these Terms and agree to the terms, conditions, and notices contained or referenced herein. They may be modified by the Companies from time to time, at their sole discretion, with such modifications to be effective upon posting by the Companies on the Website or via the Service or providing you with notice of the modification. It is important that you review such modifications because if you continue to use the Service after we have posted the modifications, you indicate that you agree to be bound by the modified Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Consent to Electronic Disclosures.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You agree that the Companies may send the following to you by email or posting them on the Website: these Terms, including legal disclosures; future changes to these Terms; Eden Health’s Privacy Policy; Eden Health’s HIPAA Policy; and other notices, legal communications or disclosures and information related to the Service (the &amp;ldquo;Communications&amp;rdquo;). You consent to receive these Communications electronically. You agree to notify us promptly if your email address changes. Your consent to conduct actions electronically and our agreement to do so covers all actions you conduct through the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Withdrawing Your Consent.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; If you later decide that you do not want to receive future Communications electronically, please send an email to  admin@getedenhealth.com or a letter to Eden Health, Inc., 108 Reade Street Suite 4F, New York, New York 10013. Your withdrawal of consent shall be effective within a reasonable time after we receive your withdrawal notice described above. Your withdrawal of consent will not affect the legal validity or enforceability of the Terms provided to, and electronically signed by, you prior to the effective date of your withdrawal. However, if you withdraw your consent to receive Communications electronically, we may terminate your use of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;eligibility&#34;&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years of age and have the right, authority and capacity to enter into these Terms and to abide by all of the terms and conditions of these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;account-registration-and-security&#34;&gt;Account Registration and Security&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to use any features of the Service, you will have to create a User account via the App. It is important that you provide us with accurate, complete and up-to-date information for your account and you agree to update such information, as needed, to keep it accurate, complete and up-to-date. You are also responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the username and password that you designate during the registration process for your account, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your account. You agree to (a) immediately notify the Companies of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. If you do not, we might have to suspend or terminate your account. The Companies will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;term-and-termination&#34;&gt;Term and Termination&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Terms will remain in full force and effect while you are a User. You may terminate your use of the Service at any time by contacting us via letter at Eden Health Inc., 108 Reade Street Suite 4F, New York, New York 10026 or via email at admin@getedenhealth.com. The Companies in their sole discretion may terminate your use of the Service at any time, including, but not limited to, if you breach these Terms, by sending notice to you at the email address you provide via the Service. If the Companies terminate your use of the Service because you have breached these Terms, you and your employer will not be entitled to any refund of paid fees. All decisions regarding the termination of accounts shall be made in the sole discretion of the Companies. The Companies are not required to provide you with notice prior to terminating your use of the Service and are not required, and may be prohibited, from disclosing a reason for the termination of your account. Even after termination, these Terms will remain in effect such that all terms that by their nature may survive termination shall be deemed to survive such termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, limitations of liability, and dispute resolution provisions. In addition, you understand and acknowledge that following termination of your account, the Companies may be required to, and will, maintain electronic copies of your medical records in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;non-commercial-user-of-the-service&#34;&gt;Non-commercial User of the Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Service is for the personal use of individual Users only and may not be used in connection with any commercial endeavors. Organizations, companies, and/or businesses are not permitted to, and should not use the Service. Illegal and/or unauthorized uses of the Service, including collecting usernames and/or email addresses of Users by electronic or other means for the purpose of sending unsolicited email and unauthorized framing of or linking to the Website, App or Service, may be investigated, and appropriate legal action will be taken, including without limitation, civil, criminal, and injunctive redress. Use of the Service is with the permission of the Companies, which may be revoked at any time, for any reason, in the Companies’ sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;feedback&#34;&gt;Feedback&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We welcome feedback, comments and suggestions for improvements to the Service (&amp;ldquo;Feedback&amp;rdquo;). You can submit Feedback by emailing us at feedback@getedenhealth.com. You grant to us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, fully-paid, royalty-free, sublicensable and transferable license under any and all intellectual property rights that you own or control to use, copy, modify, create derivative works based upon and otherwise exploit the Feedback for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-and-software-on-the-service&#34;&gt;Content and Software on the Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Proprietary Rights; License.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Eden Health, Inc. or its licensors exclusively own and retain all proprietary rights, title and interest in the Website, the App and the Service, including the Software (defined below) and all associated intellectual property rights contained therein. The Website, the App and the Service contain the copyrighted material, trademarks, and other proprietary information of Eden Health, Inc., and its licensors. Subject to the terms and conditions of these Terms, Eden Health grants to you a personal, limited, non-exclusive, nontransferable, non-sublicensable license to (i) download and install a copy of the software and technology that enable the App, together with any updates and bug fixes (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;) on a mobile device and (ii) access and use the graphics, audio, messages, photos or profiles and works of authorship of any kind that Eden Health provides or makes available via the Service (the &amp;ldquo;Content&amp;rdquo;) during the term of these Terms solely in connection with your permitted use of the Website, the App and the Service and solely for your personal and non-commercial purposes. Eden Health and its licensors retain all rights not expressly granted to you in these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Restrictions.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You shall not, and you shall not enable any third party, to (i) access or attempt to access any other systems, programs or data of the Companies that are not available for public use; (ii) copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit or distribute any Content that is not User Content; (iii) work around any technical limitations in the Software, or decompile, disassemble or otherwise reverse engineer the Software except as otherwise permitted by applicable law; (iv) perform or attempt to perform any actions that could interfere with the proper operation of the Software or Service, prevent access to or use of the Software or Service by the Companies’ other licensees or clients, or impose an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure; (v) remove, alter or obscure any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the Service (including the Software); or (vi) otherwise use the Software except as expressly allowed under this Section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reliance on Content, Advice, Etc.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Opinions, advice, statements, offers, or other information or Content made available through the Service, are those of their respective authors, and should not necessarily be relied upon. Such authors are solely responsible for such Content. The Companies do not: (i) guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any third party Content on the Service, or (ii) adopt, endorse or accept responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice, or statement made by any party that appears on the Service. Under no circumstances will the Companies or their affiliates be responsible for any loss or damage resulting from your reliance on third-party information or other Content posted on the Website or the App or transmitted to or by any Users via the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;prohibited-activities&#34;&gt;Prohibited Activities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following is a partial list of the type of actions that you may not engage in with respect to the Service:
* You will not use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or process to download, access, retrieve, index, &amp;ldquo;data mine&amp;rdquo;, or in any way reproduce or circumvent, avoid, bypass, remove, or deactivate the navigational structure or technical measures or presentation of the Service or its contents;
* You will not interfere, access, tamper with or disrupt the Service, Website or App or the servers or networks connected to the Service, Website, or App;
* You will not attempt to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of any Eden Health system or network or breach any security or authentication measures;
* You will not send any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, email, junk mail, spam, chain letters or other form of solicitation;
* You will not use any meta tags or other hidden text or metadata utilizing the Companies’ trademarks, logos, URLs or product names without the Companies’ express written consent;
* You will not use the Service, Website, App or Content, or any portion thereof, for any commercial purpose or for the benefit of any third party or in any manner not permitted by these Terms;
* You will not post, email or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;
* You will not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any information transmitted through the Service;
* You will not use, display, &amp;ldquo;frame&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;mirror&amp;rdquo; any part of the Service, the Companies’ names, any Companies’ trademarks, logos or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page, without prior written authorization from the Companies. You also shall not use meta tags or code or other devices containing any reference to the Companies or the Service in order to direct any person to any other web site for any purpose; and
* You will not collect or store any personally identifiable information from Users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;financial-policy-and-payment-agreement&#34;&gt;Financial Policy and Payment Agreement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;General.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You agree to pay the Companies all charges at the prices then in effect for any use of the Service by you or other persons (including your agents), and you authorize the Companies to use and/or disclose your health information which specifically identifies you or which can reasonable be used to identify you to carry out payment of all charges. Payment includes but is not limited to: the authorization of payment directly to the Companies of benefits otherwise payable to you. You hereby acknowledge the release of your medical records to third party insurers or authorized persons to whom disclosure is necessary to establish or collect a fee for the services provided, such as billing and collection services, insurance payers, auto accident insurers, or for work related injury to your employer or designee. You agree to forward to the Companies, all insurance or third party payments that you receive for services rendered to you immediately upon receipt. You agree that you are financially responsible for charges not covered by third party payers. The Companies reserve the right to correct any errors or mistakes that they make even if they have already requested or received payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Current Information Required.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; YOU MUST PROVIDE CURRENT, COMPLETE AND ACCURATE INFORMATION FOR YOUR ACCOUNT. YOU MUST PROMPTLY UPDATE ALL INFORMATION TO KEEP YOUR ACCOUNT CURRENT, COMPLETE AND ACCURATE (SUCH AS A CHANGE IN BILLING ADDRESS, CREDIT CARD NUMBER, OR CREDIT CARD EXPIRATION DATE OR A CHANGE IN THIRD PARTY INSURANCE PARTICIPATION, PLAN, OR COVERAGE), AND YOU MUST PROMPTLY NOTIFY THE COMPANIES IF YOUR PAYMENT METHOD (E.G., CREDIT CARD OR DEBIT CARD) IS CANCELED (E.G., FOR LOSS OR THEFT) OR IF YOU BECOME AWARE OF A POTENTIAL BREACH OF SECURITY, SUCH AS THE UNAUTHORIZED DISCLOSURE OR USE OF YOUR USER NAME OR PASSWORD. YOU MUST PROMPTLY NOTIFY THE COMPANIES IF YOUR COVERAGE BY A THIRD PARTY INSURER OR OTHER AUTHORIZED PAYER IS CANCELED. CHANGES TO SUCH INFORMATION CAN BE MADE THROUGH BY CONTACTING EDEN VIA PHONE OR EMAIL. IF YOU FAIL TO PROVIDE THE COMPANIES ANY OF THE FOREGOING INFORMATION, YOU AGREE THAT THE COMPANIES MAY CONTINUE CHARGING YOU FOR ANY USE OF THE SERVICE UNDER YOUR ACCOUNT UNLESS YOU HAVE TERMINATED YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE (CONFIRMED BY YOU IN WRITING UPON REQUEST BY THE COMPANIES).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Payment Method.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; If the Companies do not receive payment from third party insurers or other authorized payers, you agree to pay all amounts due on your account upon demand. You agree that your third party insurers and other authorized payers may impose terms and conditions on you, which are independent of these Terms and you agree to comply with all of those terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;d. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reaffirmation of Authorization.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; YOUR NON-TERMINATION OR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICE REAFFIRMS THAT THE COMPANIES ARE AUTHORIZED TO CHARGE YOU FOR SERVICES RENDERED. THE COMPANIES MAY SUBMIT THOSE CHARGES FOR PAYMENT AND YOU WILL BE RESPONSIBLE FOR SUCH CHARGES. THIS DOES NOT WAIVE THE COMPANIES’ RIGHT TO SEEK PAYMENT DIRECTLY FROM YOU. YOUR CHARGES MAY BE PAYABLE IN ADVANCE, IN ARREARS, OR PER USAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;appointments-missed-late-cancellation&#34;&gt;Appointments: Missed/Late Cancellation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You understand and agree that if you do not show for your appointment or you cancel your appointment with less than 24 hours’ notice, the Companies reserve the right to charge you a fee for a missed/late cancelled appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;modifications-to-service&#34;&gt;Modifications to Service&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Companies reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that the Companies shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;blocking-of-ip-addresses&#34;&gt;Blocking of IP Addresses&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to protect the integrity of the Service, the Companies reserve the right at any time in their sole discretion to block Users from certain IP addresses from accessing the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;copyright-policy&#34;&gt;Copyright Policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Companies respect copyright law and expect their Users to do the same. It is the Companies’ policy to terminate in appropriate circumstances Users who repeatedly infringe or are believed to be repeatedly infringing the rights of copyright holders. Please see the Companies’ Copyright Policy in our &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/terms&#34;&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy&#34;&gt;Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For information on how we collect, use and disclosure information from our Users, please refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/privacy&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/policies/hipaa&#34;&gt;HIPAA Policy&lt;/a&gt;, which are incorporated by reference as though fully set forth herein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;disclaimers&#34;&gt;Disclaimers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Companies are not responsible for any incorrect or inaccurate Content posted on the Service. The Companies are not responsible for the conduct, whether online or offline, of any User. The Companies assume no responsibility for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, or alteration of any Communication. The Companies are not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of email or players on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website or combination thereof, including injury or damage to Users’ or to any other person&amp;rsquo;s computer related to or resulting from participating or downloading materials in connection with the Service. Under no circumstances will the Companies or any of their affiliates, advertisers, promoters or distribution partners be responsible for any loss or damage, including personal injury or death, resulting from anyone&amp;rsquo;s use of the Service, any Content posted on the Service or transmitted to Users, or any interactions between Users of the Service, whether online or offline. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS-IS&amp;rdquo; AND THE COMPANIES EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. The Companies cannot guarantee and do not promise any specific results from use of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the preceding paragraph and other provisions of these Terms, any general advice that may be posted on the Website, the App or the Service is for informational purposes only and is not intended to replace or substitute for any medical or other advice. The Companies make no representations or warranties and expressly disclaim any and all liability concerning any treatment, action by, or affect on any person following the general information offered or provided within or through the Website, the App or the Service. If you have specific concerns or a situation arises in which you require medical advice, you should consult directly with one of our appropriately trained and qualified medical services providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Companies make no representation that the Service is appropriate, or is available for use outside the U.S. Access to and use of the Service where the access or use of the Service is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access and use the Service from outside the U.S. do so on their own initiative, at their own risk, and are responsible for compliance with applicable laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;permission-to-treat-telehealth-medical-treatment&#34;&gt;Permission to Treat/Telehealth Medical Treatment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By clicking &amp;ldquo;Accept&amp;rdquo; during the account registration process, you give permission to the health care providers of Eden Health to medically care for you in person, and, if applicable, by Telehealth (defined below), as applicable and appropriate. You may withdraw this consent at any time by both terminating your account and no longer seeking care from Eden Health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You understand that part of the Service requires release of your personal health information, including test results, to an online personal health record (in accordance with our HIPAA Policy) and communication with Eden Health healthcare team electronically via the Service or the App. You consent to receive emails, SMS messages, phone calls or other communications from us pertaining to your care and your health (such as automated health reminders). You hereby authorize Eden Health to use and/or disclose my health information which specifically identifies you or which can reasonably be used to identify you to carry out your treatment and other healthcare operations. “Healthcare Operations” include but are not limited to: release of your medical information to any of your physicians and their offices or insurance companies participating in your care or treatment and the quality of that care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Health Information Exchanges” (HIEs) share information about people’s health electronically and securely to improve the quality of health care services. You authorize the Companies and the health care providers listed on the Website at www.getedenhealth.com/policies/HIE (“HIE Participants”) to obtain access to your medical records through a computer network. This can collect the medical records you have in different places where you get health care, and make them available electronically to the providers treating you. The Companies may update, at their sole discretion, the list of HIE Participants. You authorize employees, agents or members of the medical staff of the Companies to see and obtain access to your electronic health records through Healthix, which is a Health Information Exchange, or Regional Health Information Organization (RHIO), a not-for-profit organization recognized by the State of New York. This consent gives your permission for any the Companies to access your records from your other healthcare providers authorized to disclose information through Healthix. You have the right to opt-out of this consent if you provide the Companies with written notice of your desire to do so by email or regular mail at admin@getedenhealth.com or Eden Health, 108 Reade Street Suite 4F, New York, NY 10013 within thirty (30) days following the date you first accept these Terms (such notice, an &amp;ldquo;HIE Opt-out Notice&amp;rdquo;). If you don’t provide the Companies with an HIE Opt-out Notice within the thirty (30) day period, you will be deemed to have knowingly and intentionally waived your right to opt-out of the HIE consent as expressly set forth above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You understand that this is given in advance of any specific diagnosis or treatment and that these services are voluntary and that you have the right to refuse these services. This consent is to be continuing in nature even after a specific diagnosis has been made and treatment recommended. This consent will remain in full force unless revoked in writing and will not affect any actions that were taken prior to receiving your revocation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You understand that virtual encounters with Eden Health or our Telehealth services via phone, email, the App or otherwise, could involve, and you hereby consent to the use of, automated tools for diagnosis, care, treatment or communication pertaining to healthcare matters. You also acknowledge that such virtual encounters with Eden Health may be provided by a variety of healthcare providers, including physicians, Registered Nurses, Nurse Practitioners, phlebotomists, and other support or medical personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Website, the App and Telehealth services are NOT appropriate for emergency or urgent medical matters. You agree that for all urgent or emergency matters that you believe may immediately affect your health, you will immediately contact your medical services provider, call 911 or go to an emergency room at a local hospital facility.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Telehealth&amp;rdquo; is the delivery of healthcare services using technology when the healthcare provider and patient are not in the same physical location, and/or the virtual delivery of healthcare services, including by a medical provider or via digital or automated tools, including without limitation tools for medical or health-related diagnosis and treatment. Telehealth may be used for diagnosis, treatment, follow-up and/or patient education, and may include, without limitation, the following: electronic transmission of patient medical records, medical images, or other patient data; synchronous (i.e., &amp;ldquo;real time&amp;rdquo;) and asynchronous (i.e., non-&amp;ldquo;real time&amp;rdquo;) interactions via audio, video, and/or data communications; automated or digital tools for diagnosis, care, treatment and/or communication pertaining to healthcare or medical matters; and output data from medical devices, sound and video files. Further, you understand that it may be possible that your condition cannot be treated via Telehealth, or that information transmitted through Telehealth may not be sufficient or of too poor of image quality, or insufficient information or data to allow for appropriate medical decision making. Accordingly, you may be required to seek additional in-person medical care, alternative healthcare or emergency services. You agree that if your health or medical problem or condition persists after use of Telehealth via the App, you will immediately contact your medical services provider and seek appropriate additional in-person medical care or emergency care, as appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;links-and-third-party-applications&#34;&gt;Links and Third Party Applications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Service may provide, or third parties may provide, links to other sites or other online resources. In addition, our Website or App may also integrate third-party applications, products or services (the &amp;ldquo;Third Party Applications&amp;rdquo;), which may have access to your data and protected health information (&amp;ldquo;PHI&amp;rdquo;). These third parties are not affiliated with us and may have different policies with respect to handling your data and PHI, and use of such Third-Party Applications is subject to their applicable terms and conditions and privacy policies. We are not responsible for and do not make any representations or warranties with respect to any third party technology or Third Party Applications, or the actions or inactions of such third parties, accessible via the App, Service or the Website. Any purchase by you of any Third Party Applications or any exchange of data or other interaction between you and a provider of a Third Party Application is solely between you and the applicable third-party service provider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the Companies have no control over such Third Party Applications and third-party sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that the Companies are not responsible for the availability, quality, accuracy, integrity, safety, reliability or legality of such external sites or resources, and do not endorse and are not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Third Party Applications, sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that the Companies shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage, harm, injury or loss of any kind caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the purchase, use of, download, installation or reliance upon, any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site, Third Party Application or resource.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not endorse and are not responsible for the information and security practices or privacy policies of Third Party Applications or web sites operated by others that may be linked to or from the Service, Website or App. No web sites that link to the Service may frame or otherwise incorporate the Content on the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;limitation-on-liability&#34;&gt;Limitation on Liability&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL THE COMPANIES (OR THEIR EMPLOYEES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS OR AGENTS) BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RELATING TO LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA OR LOSS OF GOODWILL, SERVICE INTERRUPTION, COMPUTER DAMAGE OR SYSTEM FAILURE, THE COST OF SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, BODILY INJURY OR DEATH, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS OR FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE, APP, SERVICE OR SOFTWARE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, WARRANTY, PRODUCT LIABILITY, TORT OR OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND EVEN IF THE COMPANIES HAVE BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING TO THE CONTRARY CONTAINED HEREIN, THE COMPANIES’ LIABILITY TO YOU ARISING FROM THESE TERMS, OR THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE, APP, SERVICE OR SOFTWARE, WILL AT ALL TIMES BE LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF USD $100.00 OR THE AMOUNTS PAID BY YOU OR YOUR EMPLOYER TO THE COMPANIES FOR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SERVICE. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;u-s-export-controls&#34;&gt;U.S. Export Controls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree to comply fully with all U.S. and foreign export laws and regulations to ensure that neither the Software nor any technical data related thereto nor any direct product thereof is exported or re-exported directly or indirectly in violation of, or used for any purposes prohibited by, such laws and regulations. By using the Service, you represent and warrant that: (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a &amp;ldquo;terrorist supporting&amp;rdquo; country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dispute-resolution&#34;&gt;Dispute Resolution&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Governing Law&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Terms and any action related thereto will be governed by the laws of the State of New York without regard to its conflict of laws provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Agreement to Arbitrate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and the Companies agree that any dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or relating to these Terms or the breach, termination, enforcement, interpretation or validity thereof or the use of the Service (collectively, &amp;ldquo;Disputes&amp;rdquo;) will be settled by binding arbitration, except that each party retains the right: (i) to bring an individual action in small claims court, and (ii) to seek injunctive or other equitable relief in a court of competent jurisdiction to prevent the actual or threatened infringement, misappropriation or violation of a party’s copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents or other intellectual property rights (the action described in the foregoing clause (ii), an (&amp;ldquo;IP Protection Action&amp;rdquo;). Without limiting the preceding sentence, you will also have the right to litigate any other Dispute if you provide the Companies with written notice of your desire to do so by email or regular mail at admin@getedenhealth.com or Eden Health, 108 Reade Street Suite 4F, New York, NY 10013 within thirty (30) days following the date you first accept these Terms (such notice, an &amp;ldquo;Arbitration Opt-out Notice&amp;rdquo;). If you don’t provide the Companies with an Arbitration Opt-out Notice within the thirty (30) day period, you will be deemed to have knowingly and intentionally waived your right to litigate any Dispute except as expressly set forth in clauses (i) and (ii) above. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue of any IP Protection Action or, if you timely provide the Companies with an Arbitration Opt-out Notice, will be the state and federal courts located in the Southern District of New York and each of the parties hereto waives any objection to jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Unless you timely provide the Companies with an Arbitration Opt-out Notice, you acknowledge and agree that you and the Companies are each waiving the right to a trial by jury or to participate as a plaintiff or class member in any purported class action or representative proceeding. Further, unless both you and the Companies otherwise agree in writing, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person&amp;rsquo;s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of any class or representative proceeding. If this specific paragraph is held unenforceable, then the entirety of this &amp;ldquo;Dispute Resolution&amp;rdquo; section will be deemed void. Except as provided in the preceding sentence, this &amp;ldquo;Dispute Resolution&amp;rdquo; section will survive any termination of these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Arbitration Rules&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arbitration will be administered by the American Arbitration Association (&amp;ldquo;AAA&amp;rdquo;) in accordance with the Commercial Arbitration Rules and the Supplementary Procedures for Consumer Related Disputes (the &amp;ldquo;AAA Rules&amp;rdquo;) then in effect, except as modified by this &amp;ldquo;Dispute Resolution&amp;rdquo; section. (The AAA Rules are available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.adr.org/arb_med&#34;&gt;http://www.adr.org/arb_med&lt;/a&gt; or by calling the AAA at 1-800-778-7879.) The Federal Arbitration Act will govern the interpretation and enforcement of this Section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Arbitration Process&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A party who desires to initiate arbitration must provide the other party with a written Demand for Arbitration as specified in the AAA Rules. AAA provides a general form for a Demand for Arbitration and a separate form for Demand for Arbitration for California residents. The arbitrator will be either a retired judge or an attorney licensed to practice law and will be selected by the parties from the AAA’s roster of arbitrators. If the parties are unable to agree upon an arbitrator within seven (7) days of delivery of the Demand for Arbitration, then the AAA will appoint the arbitrator in accordance with the AAA Rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Arbitration Location and Procedure&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you and the Companies otherwise agree, the arbitration will be conducted in the county where you reside. If your claim does not exceed $10,000, then the arbitration will be conducted solely on the basis of the documents that you and the Companies submit to the arbitrator, unless you request a hearing or the arbitrator determines that a hearing is necessary. If your claim exceeds $10,000, your right to a hearing will be determined by the AAA Rules. Subject to the AAA Rules, the arbitrator will have the discretion to direct a reasonable exchange of information by the parties, consistent with the expedited nature of the arbitration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Arbitrator&amp;rsquo;s Decision&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arbitrator will render an award within the time frame specified in the AAA Rules. The arbitrator’s decision will include the essential findings and conclusions upon which the arbitrator based the award. Judgment on the arbitration award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator’s award of damages must be consistent with the terms of the &amp;ldquo;Limitation of Liability&amp;rdquo; section above as to the types and amounts of damages for which a party may be held liable. The arbitrator may award declaratory or injunctive relief only in favor of the claimant and only to the extent necessary to provide relief warranted by the claimant’s individual claim. If you prevail in arbitration you will be entitled to an award of attorneys’ fees and expenses, to the extent provided under applicable law. The Companies will not seek, and hereby waive all rights they may have under applicable law to recover, attorneys’ fees and expenses if they prevail in arbitration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Fees&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your responsibility to pay any AAA filing, administrative and arbitrator fees will be solely as set forth in the AAA Rules. However, if your claim for damages does not exceed $75,000, the Companies will pay all such fees unless the arbitrator finds that either the substance of your claim or the relief sought in your Demand for Arbitration was frivolous or was brought for an improper purpose (as measured by the standards set forth in Federal Rule of Civil Procedure 11(b)).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Changes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in these Terms, if the Companies change this &amp;ldquo;Dispute Resolution&amp;rdquo; section after the date you first accepted these Terms (or accepted any subsequent changes to these Terms), you may reject any such change by sending us written notice (including by email to admin@getedenhealth.com within 30 days of the date such change became effective, as indicated in the &amp;ldquo;Last Updated&amp;rdquo; date above or in the date of the Companies’ email to you notifying you of such change. By rejecting any change, you are agreeing that you will arbitrate any Dispute between you and the Companies in accordance with the provisions of this &amp;ldquo;Dispute Resolution&amp;rdquo; section as of the date you first accepted these Terms (or accepted any subsequent changes to these Terms).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;indemnity-by-you&#34;&gt;Indemnity by You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree to defend, indemnify and hold the Companies, their subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, and other partners and employees, harmless from any loss, liability, claim, or demand, including, without limitation, reasonable attorney&amp;rsquo;s fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the Service in violation of these Terms and/or arising from a breach of these Terms and/or any breach of your representations and warranties set forth above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-third-party-beneficiaries&#34;&gt;No Third Party Beneficiaries&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree that, except as otherwise expressly provided in these Terms, there shall be no third party beneficiaries to these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;waiver-and-severability&#34;&gt;Waiver and Severability&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The failure of the Companies to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not constitute a waiver of future enforcement of that right or provision. The waiver of any such right or provision will be effective only if in writing and signed by a duly authorized representative of the Companies. Except as expressly set forth in these Terms, the exercise by any party of any of its remedies under these Terms will be without prejudice to its other remedies under these Terms or otherwise. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction or an arbitrator finds any provision of these Terms invalid or unenforceable, that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible and the other provisions of these Terms will remain in full force and effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;entire-agreement&#34;&gt;Entire Agreement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Terms constitute the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between the Companies and you regarding the Service, and these Terms supersede and replace any and all prior oral or written understandings or agreements between the Companies and you regarding the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;assignment&#34;&gt;Assignment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may not assign or transfer these Terms, by operation of law or otherwise, without the Companies’ prior written consent. Any attempt by you to assign or transfer these Terms, without such consent, will be null and of no effect. The Companies may assign or transfer these Terms, at their sole discretion, without restriction. Subject to the foregoing, these Terms will bind and inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;notices&#34;&gt;Notices&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any notices or other communications permitted or required hereunder, including those regarding modifications to these Terms, will be in writing and given by the Companies (i) via email (in each case to the address that you have provided); or (ii) by posting to the Website or the App or via the Service. For notices made by e-mail, the date of receipt will be deemed the date on which such notice is transmitted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-information&#34;&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these Terms or the Service, please contact the Companies at admin@getedenhealth.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED ABOVE.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- container --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;eden-section about&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;five columns&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;We&#39;re bringing healthcare to its roots: the relationship between the patient and the doctor.&lt;/h4&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;six columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          The average primary care physician in the US supports 2,500 patients at any given time. Patients wait 18 days on average for a doctor&#39;s appointment, and physicians are able to see patients for only 11 minutes.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          We’re flipping the model on its head to provide better care while, at the same time, decreasing costs to employers and the health system at large.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;ten columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Team&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/matt-mccambridge.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Matt McCambridge, CEO&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Matt is Chief Executive Officer of Eden Health. Previously, he was a technology and software investor at Insight Venture Partners, a leading global venture capital and private equity firm that has raised over $13 billion. Matt is also a board member at Areté Education and leads their effort to build a boarding school for high school students in the South Bronx. Matt earned his bachelor&#39;s degree from Harvard University and taught at the Kennedy School of Government under Ron Heifetz.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/benjamin-stein.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Benjamin Stein, MD, CMO&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Dr. Ben is Chief Medical Officer of Eden Health and a practicing physician. Previously, he was Lead Physician at GoHealth Urgent Care, helping the organization grow from zero to over thirty sites in the greater New York area. Before that, Dr. Ben was founder and CEO of Healthix, now the nations largest health information exchange. He has also worked as the Director of Clinical Systems at Northwell Health, the second largest not-for-profit health system in the US. Dr. Ben received his bachelor&#39;s degree in computer science from Brown University and his medical degree from Georgetown University School of Medicine.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/scott-sansovich.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Scott Sansovich, CPO&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Scott is Chief Product Officer of Eden Health. Previously, he was a product manager at AppNexus, the advertising technology company based in New York City, and was an investment associate at the venture capital firm Cue Ball, where he focused on enterprise software. He also co-founded The Resume Drop, a recruiting platform that connected students at universities, including all eight Ivy League schools, to jobs in the technology sector. Scott earned his bachelor&#39;s from Harvard University.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/jonathan-stevens.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Jonathan Stevens, Data Analyst&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        Jonathan is a data analyst at Eden Health. He is responsible for population health analysis and analyses related to improvements in quality and value of care. Previously, he worked at the National Museum of Mathematics and as a private educator focusing on secondary and tertiary mathematics and economics education. Jonathan received his bachelor&#39;s degree in Applied Mathematics from Harvard University.
      &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;ten columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Advisory Board&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/aran-ron.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Aran Ron, MD&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Aran Ron is a physician trained in internal medicine at New York Hospital. He is one of the original founders and until recently the Chief Medical Officer of Oscar Health Plan and of Pager. He is the former President and Chief Operating Officer of Group Health Inc.,  a $3 billion health plan, was Medical Director at Oxford Health Plan and at New York Downtown Hospital. He served as CEO of Partners Health Plan (a special needs MLTC plan) and an Operating Partner at Bessemer Venture Partners.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div id=&#34;aran-ron&#34; style=&#34;display:none;&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          His background includes board certification and licensure in internal medicine, degrees in business and public health. He has published articles in medical journals, and serves on local and national committees, and on the board of director’s and advisory boards including Group Health Inc (term ended 3/12), formerly Data Driven Delivery Systems, Nalari, Dunn Meadow Pharmacy, Israel BioMed Fund, LifeForce Capital Fund as well as non-for-profits St Christopher Inc and Metropolitan Council on Poverty.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          He is on the URAC accreditation committee and lectures at Cornell Medical College (where he received a best teacher of the year award) and Columbia Business School.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a onclick=&#34;toggle(&#39;aran-ron&#39;, this)&#34;&gt;+ Show more&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/mary-ellen-connington.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Mary Ellen Connington, MA, RN&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Mary Ellen Connington is an experienced senior healthcare executive, recognized for leadership in health plans, hospitals and provider organizations. She is Chief Operating Officer at Advocate Care Physicians, the largest DSRIP in New York state. She was most recently SVP for Quality and Medical Management at Oscar, where she was responsible for the company’s Quality/UM/Case and Disease Management programs.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div id=&#34;mary-ellen-connington&#34; style=&#34;display:none;&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        She was SVP of Managed Care at The Visiting Nurse Service of New York, leading the $3B revenue organization’s strategic plan for interfacing with the health insurance industry, and was also VP of Managed Care at EmblemHealth.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        She earned her MA from Columbia University (summa cum laude) and her BSN (cum laude) from College of Mount Saint Vincent.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a onclick=&#34;toggle(&#39;mary-ellen-connington&#39;, this)&#34;&gt;+ Show more&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/laurel-pickering.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Laurel Pickering&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Laurel Pickering is a leader and visionary, devoted to transforming healthcare at both regional and national levels. As President &amp; CEO of Northeast Business Group on Health (NEBGH), Ms. Pickering has built an employer-led coalition of healthcare leaders and other stakeholders with the mission of empowering members to drive excellence and value in healthcare and the patient experience. NEBGH currently has 170 members comprised of national and global self-insured employers based in New York, New Jersey, Connecticut and Massachusetts; plus national health plans, major consulting organizations, regional hospital systems and other key stakeholders.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div id=&#34;laurel-pickering&#34; style=&#34;display:none;&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Under Laurel&#39;s leadership, NEBGH has become one of the most active and influential healthcare-focused business coalitions in the country, focused on moving toward a value-based delivery system. NEBGH delivers educational and training programs for benefits executives, user groups designed to help them improve health plan and PBM performance, and guidance on private exchanges via the Private Exchange Evaluation Collaborative (PEEC), of which Ms. Pickering is a founder.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Multi-payer efforts initiated by NEBGH include reducing unnecessary hospital readmissions, piloting an integrated approach to behavioral health in primary care in NYC, and developing innovative solutions to obesity, diabetes and other workplace health concerns through NEBGH’s Solutions Center.  Based on these efforts, NEBGH has been enlisted by New York State’s Department of Health to play a key role in promoting a new advanced primary care model funded by a federal State Innovation Model (SIM) grant.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        On the national level, Ms. Pickering is Chair of the Board of Directors of The Leapfrog Group, and serves on the Board of National Quality Forum (NQF) and National Business Coalition on Health (NBCH). Regionally, she is Chair of the Board of Directors of the NEBGH subsidiary HealthPass, a health insurance exchange for small businesses.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Ms. Pickering received her BA in Anthropology from SUNY Albany and MPH from Emory University.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a onclick=&#34;toggle(&#39;laurel-pickering&#39;, this)&#34;&gt;+ Show more&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row person&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;two columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/headshots/jeffrey-sachs.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eight columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;p class=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Jeffrey Sachs&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Jeffrey Sachs is a leading health care policy expert who has worked with hospitals, health systems, health plans, behavioral health organizations, technology companies, unions, federal and state governments, and others for more than three decades.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div id=&#34;jeffrey-sachs&#34; style=&#34;display:none;&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Dr. Sachs was one of the architects of the recent New York State Medicaid Redesign Team process and its accompanying $8 billion Medicaid waiver. The result was one of the nation’s most innovative and comprehensive Medicaid overhauls.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        In 2014, Dr. Sachs negotiated an agreement between the California Hospital Association and the SEIU/UHW which resulted in the establishment of a $100 million advocacy fund to support Medi-Cal. He also provided guidance on the development of California’s 2010 $10 billion Medicaid waiver.
        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        In 2009, Dr. Sachs participated on President Obama’s Health Policy Advisory Committee on federal health care reform. He facilitated a joint letter signed by AHIP, PhARMA, AMA, AdvaMed, AHA and SEIU expressing support for health care reform initiatives that would decrease the annual health care spending growth rate by 1.5 percentage points as part of the negotiations around the ACA.
        &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;a onclick=&#34;toggle(&#39;jeffrey-sachs&#39;, this)&#34;&gt;+ Show more&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- container --&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  function toggle(id, link) {
    var el = document.getElementById(id);
    if ( el.style.display != &#39;none&#39; ) {
      el.style.display = &#39;none&#39;;
      link.innerHTML = &#39;+ Show more&#39;
    }
    else {
      el.style.display = &#39;&#39;;
      link.innerHTML = &#39;- Show less&#39;
    }
  }
&lt;/script&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;eden-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h1&gt;Contact us&lt;/h1&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;five columns&#34;&gt;
        General &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;info@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Employers &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:employers@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;employers@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Members &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:members@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;members@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Partnerships &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:partners@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;partners@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Media &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:media@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;media@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Careers &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:careers@getedenhealth.com&#34;&gt;careers@getedenhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;strong&gt;Address&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        Eden Health, Inc.&lt;br&gt;
        442 Broadway, 2nd Floor&lt;br&gt;
        New York, NY 10013&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/dir//442+Broadway,+New+York,+NY+10013/@40.7200541,-74.0016612,16.72z/data=!4m16!1m7!3m6!1s0x89c2598a264f8db7:0x9b2e342b7093666b!2s442+Broadway,+New+York,+NY+10013!3b1!8m2!3d40.7200729!4d-74.0008091!4m7!1m0!1m5!1m1!1s0x89c2598a264f8db7:0x9b2e342b7093666b!2m2!1d-74.0008091!2d40.7200729&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
          Directions
        &lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;seven columns&#34;&gt;
        &lt;iframe class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; style=&#34;background-color:#f0f0f0&#34; src=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3660.580997019633!2d-74.0016612100705!3d40.72005407190789!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x89c2598a264f8db7%3A0x9b2e342b7093666b!2s442+Broadway%2C+New+York%2C+NY+10013!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1483724500504&#34; width=&#34;600&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;border:0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- container --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employees</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/howitworks/employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/howitworks/employees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-hero&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;seven columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h1&gt;Healthcare like you’ve never experienced it before.&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As an Eden Health member, you have a team of doctors and nurses at your side. You can see us both in-person and virtually, at no cost and as often as you’d like.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;With Eden Health, you also have unlimited access to our virtual health concierge, who will help answer, track down, and coordinate anything related to your health.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eden-desktop three columns offset-by-two&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/iphone.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;six columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;eden-mobile&#34;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/office.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Modern, personal healthcare&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Eden Health members enjoy unlimited visits at our beautiful offices - with no out of pocket costs.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We provide the full range of primary care services:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/thermometer-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Preventative and chronic care&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/bandage-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Acute care and minor injuries&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/behavioral-health-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Behavioral health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/allergen-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Allergies and allergic reactions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/ekg-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Annual physicals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/heart-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Women&#39;s health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/skin-bump-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Skin conditions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;service&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/beaker-icon.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Labs and screenings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eden-desktop six columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/office.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;three columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/iphone.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;seven columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Virtual healthcare concierge&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some examples of requests we can handle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&#34;Can I see the doctor today between 2pm and 5pm?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“Do I have the flu or just a cold?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“My physical therapy isn’t working. Do I need surgery?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“My ortho said I need to get an MRI. Where should I go?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“I forgot when my last tetanus shot was. Can you track it down?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“Can you send my medical records to my endocrinologist?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“Should I be worried about this rash?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“Who’s the best physical therapist in Brooklyn?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“Where should my wife go for an OB/GYN visit?”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;“I’ve had a cough since I starting taking the meds. Is that normal?&#34;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- container --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employers</title>
      <link>http://getedenhealth.com/howitworks/employers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:50:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getedenhealth.com/howitworks/employers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-hero&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;seven columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;eden-mobile&#34;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/clinician-crest.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;h1&gt;We make healthcare work for businesses.&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Eden Health’s comprehensive approach meaningfully improves health outcomes for employees and reduces the total cost of care to employers.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For common conditions, our doctors and nurses treat patients both in-person and virtually. For more complex conditions requiring a specialist’s expertise, we refer to high-value providers who have a proven track record for high quality and high value.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eden-desktop five columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/clinician-crest.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


  &lt;div class=&#34;eden-section&#34; id=&#34;cost-savings&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;twelve columns&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Save on healthcare costs&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Eden Health removes financial and logistical barriers to receiving care. By improving &lt;strong&gt;access&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;convenience&lt;/strong&gt; for employees, we make it easy for employees to receive the right care at the right time at the right place.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;spacer&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;six columns&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce specialist overuse&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce time spent seeking and coordinating care&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce urgent care and ER use&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;six columns&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce waste from market pricing failures&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce wellness-sensitive medical events&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;arrow&#34;&gt;&amp;#x25BE;&lt;/span&gt;Reduce use of expensive brand name medications&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;six columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;eden-mobile&#34;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/employer-dashboard.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Population Health Management&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Surface prevalent conditions within the employee base. We also work with employers to implement high-impact programming that targets the specific issues that your employees are facing.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;eden-desktop six columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/employer-dashboard.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row eden-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;five columns&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img class=&#34;u-full-width&#34; src=&#34;http://getedenhealth.com/img/curation-map.jpg&#34; /&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;six columns offset-by-one&#34;&gt;
      &lt;h2&gt;Curated, value-based referrals&lt;/h2&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;We use industry-leading pricing and quality data to curate our referrals to providers that have a proven track record of high quality. These value-based referrals drive significant cost savings and improve patient satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- container --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>